{
    "subject": "resource/Nuclear_Rabbit",
    "predicate": "property/origin",
    "object": "resource/Novato,_California",
    "human_readable": "Nuclear Rabbit originates from Novato, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9086337089538574,
            "question": "Is Nuclear Rabbit from California?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8196266293525696,
            "question": "Where did Nuclear Rabbit originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8192441463470459,
            "question": "Name the place where Nuclear Rabbit originated."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231106162071228,
            "question": "What is the origin city of Nuclear Rabbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7047832608222961,
            "question": "Where can we find the origins of Nuclear Rabbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6996376514434814,
            "question": "In which state is Nuclear Rabbit from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6674790978431702,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of Nuclear Rabbit's origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6362473368644714,
            "question": "Nuclear Rabbit hails from which city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5186348557472229,
            "question": "What city is associated with Nuclear Rabbit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49596691131591797,
            "question": "What US state is Nuclear Rabbit from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nuclear Rabbit originates from Novato, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5904_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is associated with Nuclear Rabbit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5904_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nuclear Rabbit hails from which city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5904_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the location of Nuclear Rabbit's origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5904_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5904_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Nuclear Rabbit is a band started in Novato, California. Therefore, the statement \"Nuclear Rabbit originates from Novato, California\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}